[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This aircraft is used widely by the Thunderbirds and Air Force Fighter Wings.", "correct_answer": "F-16", "incorrect_answers": ["F-14", "F-15", "F-18"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1982 movie starring Meryl Streep and Kevin Kline was about a survivor of a Nazi concentration camp?", "correct_answer": "Sophies Choice", "incorrect_answers": ["Schindlers List", "The Killing Fields", "The Pianist"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The members of which profession used to be called leechers\u201d because of the methods they used in the past?", "correct_answer": "Doctors", "incorrect_answers": ["Pharmacists", "Dentists", "Lawyers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first official Postmaster General of the United States?", "correct_answer": "Samuel Osgood", "incorrect_answers": ["Ulmer Pierce Smith", "John Jay", "Ben Franklin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One slice (139g) of Dominos Classic Hand Tossed Veggie Feast pizza has more calories than Arbys Ham Biscuit (Breakfast Sandwich).", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How long does it take for the planet Mercury to orbit the Sun once?", "correct_answer": "88 days", "incorrect_answers": ["2 years", "44 days", "365 days"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these groups was formed in Liverpool, England?", "correct_answer": "The Beatles", "incorrect_answers": ["The Bee Gees", "The Kinks", "The Rolling Stones"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the most common reason for water waste?", "correct_answer": "Showers", "incorrect_answers": ["Washing Machines", "Dish Washers", "Brushing your teeth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lawyer Bob Grimes was able to get a client off the hook because of a faulty search warrant.  He says the warrant lists the house as being:", "correct_answer": "Brown, when in fact its beige and yellow.", "incorrect_answers": ["Orange, when in fact its Brown and Ecru.", "Peach, when in fact its Chartreuse and off white.", "Grey, when in fact its Maroon and Tan."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the chemical symbol for Iron?", "correct_answer": "Fe", "incorrect_answers": ["In", "Fr", "I"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which country would you find the worlds largest underground lake?", "correct_answer": "USA (Tennessee)", "incorrect_answers": ["Ukraine", "Poland", "USA (Kentucky)"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Green coffee beans can be roasted at home in less than 30 minutes.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]